Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I'll kill them!
I'll kill them all!
Traitors and villains!
- They dare strike at me!
- Your Grace.
- I am the king!
- Your Grace! Yes. yes.
- Yes. Your Grace. Uh. please. Your Grace.
Traitors and villains!
Fire from the sky.
This is war!
I declare war!
The gates have been shut.
The search
progresses.
The villain
will be found.
We mustn't be
shaken by this.
This act.
- The child.
- The child is dead.
His pain is ended.
But what they've done
to-to-to my girl.
Yes.
And they will
pay for this.
- Who will pay?
- Whosever hand did this or caused it to be done.
And what if the hand
that's done it
is not who must be blamed?
The gods punish us.
They punish me.
For what sin?
Daughter. listen to me.
We will mourn
as we must.
but... some good
may yet come of this.
And where were
the members of this council
while the murderer
threatened their king?
Were you also threatened.
Your Grace?
I could have been!
My son is my legacy!
My son is heir
to the Iron Throne!
And where
were you.
the Lord Commander
of my Kingsguard?
I was abed. Your Grace.
having ordered the Night's Watch.
Abed.
Abed!
Instead of safeguarding
the sanctity of my family!
This is not the time
for blind accusations. Your Grace.
We'll know
who did this soon enough.
Who did this?
Who d... What?!
Is there any question
who did this?!
Who would do this
save the bitch queen of bastards.
the smug cunt
of Dragonstone?
There she sits
across the bay.
on her rock.
laughing at me.
She's fucking laughing at me!
You wished her life
to be spared.
If I may.
Your Grace.
My Lords.
The guard has
detained someone.
The man we apprehended
is known to us.
He's a gold cloak.
Noted for his
brutal nature.
We caught him. fleeing
the Gate of the Gods
with the child's
head in a sack.
- I'll kill him myself.
- We'd do well to get what information we can
from the blackguard.
I trust in the mastery
of your trade. Lord Larys.
Oh. always studying.
always protocol.
- We know our enemy!
- A king may have
more than one enemy.
Your Grace.
We would do well to ascertain
if this is your sister's hand...
or if there is a serpent nestled
closer to our bosoms.
I suppose you're
right. Ironrod.
Could be anyone.
It could be any one of you
in this room.
Lord Jasper is correct.
In one sense.
we must determine what happened
and... if we in the Keep
are still in peril.
In another sense.
of course...
it doesn't matter.
You mean
to blame Rhaenyra.
Tell the realm
she has done this.
I'll have the realm
told nothing.
We were assaulted
within our own walls.
Within our own beds.
I will not
be seen as weak.
You're already seen
as weak. Aegon.
You fucking...
A hasty coronation.
a dragon escaping the pit.
The people
see an omen.
They whisper
in the streets.
They say.
perhaps Rhaenyra should be queen.
And so. you would
name her: monster.
Slayer of infants.
I would do more than that.
A funeral progress.
Let them see the child.
Let them look
upon the works
of this pretender
to the throne.
Father.
- My king...
- No.
I will not have
my little son's body
dragged through the street
like a dead dog.
Not dragged! Honored!
Escorted to
the dragon pit
to be burned
as a Targaryen prince.
Your Grace.
No.
Let no one say
I do not grieve.
Jaehaerys was my grandson.
I loved him.
I will not have
him die in vain.
Those who declared
for Rhaenyra.
will they still
support her
when they hear
of her depravity?
Or will they rather
not renounce her?
Jaehaerys will do
more for us now
than a thousand
knights in battle.
You will have your war.
Your Grace.
But if you wait
a short time.
you may yet double
your strength.
Mother.
The Hand sets on a difficult path.
my darling.
but it. it might be
the right one.
Let the Silent Sisters ready the prince
for his final journey.
And riding behind him.
his mother the Queen.
and with her.
the Queen Dowager.
No. I do not wish
to be a spectacle.
The realm must see
the sorrow of the crown.
a sorrow best expressed
through its most
gentle souls.
I think you'll all agree
the king himself must be spared.
There's to be a funeral
for Jaehaerys.
We've been asked
to ride on a wagon behind his body.
I don't want to.
Neither do I.
But when a thing
like this happens...
a blow to the king
is a blow to the realm.
When the people share our grief.
they draw closer to us.
I don't want them closer.
I don't know them.
Sometimes.
we have to pretend.
Why?
We are representatives of the throne.
We have a duty.
Helaena. what you saw last night
when you came to my room...
This is for my boy.
I was. I was hired
by Daemon Targaryen.
He paid us.
Half now. half when the job is done.
- Who is "us"?
- A-A ratcatcher.
Employed by the household.
I don't know
his right name.
Behold the works
of Rhaenyra Targaryen!
Pretender to the throne!
Kinslayer!
Deepest sympathies.
my Queen.
Gods be with you.
We support you.
Queen Helaena.
Defiler of the innocent!
Behold the works
of Rhaenyra. the cruel!
Are you gonna hurt me?
No.
But I cannot vouch
for His Grace.
Behold the works
of Rhaenyra Targaryen!
Our Queen!
Pretender to the throne!
Kinslayer!
Queen Helaena!
What's happening there?
What's going on?
Move it. then!
- Queen Helaena!
- Helaena.
Queen Helaena!
Helaena.
Heave! Heave!
A curse. a curse on Rhaenyra.
the monstrous!
It is yet unclear
how the Keep itself was breached.
The boy's head was
severed from his body.
Thousands witnessed
the procession.
And they are accusing me
of having a hand in this.
It appears so.
There have been messages
sent to that effect
throughout the realm.
We must send
our own messages.
denying this
vile allegation.
I will do so at once.
but I'm not sure they will be received
in good faith.
And we must double our guard.
here and in Driftmark.
There will be swift
retribution in one form or another...
I have seen to it.
Your Grace.
Let me fly out on Vermax.
Rhaenys is needed in the Gullet
and I can watch for movements
- from King's Landing.
- No.
It must be said
that the damage
to our position
is immeasurable.
at a time when
we most need loyalty to our cause.
B-But it's a lie.
Having lost my own son.
that I would inflict
such a thing on Helaena.
of all people...
an innocent.
The death of Prince Lucerys
was a shock and an insult.
A mother so aggrieved
might. naturally.
- seek relief in retribution.
- Are you suggesting. Ser Alfred.
that my grief drove me
to order the decapitation of a child?
I merely thought. perhaps.
an action taken in haste.
Mind yourself.
Did you send assassins
to murder children in their beds?
I sent the queen's
vengeance for her son.
What did you tell
this "vengeance"?
What did you say
to him. Daemon.
that a boy lies dead
and I am accused
- of killing it?
- Mysaria provided me with names
and a subterfuge.
I was clear
in my instructions:
Aemond. the brother
of Aegon the Usurper.
- I cannot be responsible for a mistake.
- Cannot be responsible?
If Aemond was not
to be found.
what were your
instructions then?
They did not concern.
in any way.
- that of a little child.
- You said that it was your aim
to spill Hightower blood.
and if not Aemond.
then anyone would do.
- No.
- You have wounded me.
Weakened my claim
to the throne.
my ability
to raise an army.
my standing among
my own council.
I said no.
I don't believe you.
And so we come to it.
at long last.
Cannot trust you. Daemon.
I've never trusted
you. wholly...
much though I wished to.
willed myself to.
But now I have seen
that your heart belongs only to you.
And when I was a child.
I took this as a challenge.
But I am older now.
I have challenges enough.
- I have served you faithfully.
- Have you?
Or have you used me
as a tool
with which to grasp
at your stolen inheritance?
When Ser Erryk
brought you the crown...
did I myself not place it
upon your brow?
Yes. but before that.
you sought to lead
a council of war
while I labored alone
in my bedchamber.
And afterward.
when I thought it meet to consider
- the terms our foes put before us...
- A folly! A folly!
To give up my brother's throne
to the traitorous lies
- of Otto Hightower!
- My throne. Daemon.
mine!
I think you used
my words as an excuse
to take your
own revenge...
to indulge the darkness you keep sheathed
within you like a blade.
You think me some
kind of monster...
Oh. I don't know
what to think of you.
I don't know what you are.
or who it is you serve.
Am I not
on my way. even now.
to Harrenhal to raise an army in your name.
Rhaenyra?! Yours!
Do you accept me
as your queen and ruler?
Or do you cling. even now.
to what you think you lost?
- What I think I lost?
- You did not lose it.
You gave it away...
because you thought ever and only
of your own glory.
and not of my father
in his grief
- who needed you.
- Your father was a coward
who knew I was
the stronger son.
that I was
the leader of men
and he was afraid
to be seen in my shadow.
Is that what you understand
of your own brother?
Oh. you know him
better than I do.
who was raised
at his side?
Do you believe
he made you heir
because of your
great wisdom?
Because of your virtue?
- How dare you...
- Or did he merely use you as a tool
to put me in my place
because he was
afraid of me?
Because he knew your legacy.
unlike mine.
would never
outshine his own.
He was not afraid
of you. Daemon!
He could not trust you...
any more than I can trust you.
He was a fool...
who sought greatness
but shrank from spilling blood
to achieve it.
And I see you will
suffer the same fate.
You struck down a child.
It was a mistake.
You're pathetic.
Father?
You wish to see me.
Your Grace?
When morning comes.
take Moondancer
and keep a watch
on King's Landing.
I must know
which course they take next.
I will be vigilant.
I depend on you.
Baela.
Stay high and keep
your distance.
We can afford
no further mistakes.
My father?
He must follow
his own path.
If you please.
m'lord.
Have you
told anyone?
What do you take me for?
One who seeks
absolution.
There is none
for what I've done.
What is this?
It's a reminder
of yesterday. I think.
The procession
was muddy.
- I'll replace it hence.
- Do it now.
The night was long.
Ser Criston.
- and I had not eaten...
- You defy my authority. Ser Arryk.
- I do not.
- The white cloak is a symbol of our purity...
our fidelity.
Kingsguard are
a sacred trust.
Will you so easily sully
our ancient honor?
I have erred.
my lord.
I'll remedy
the error.
Where were you
when Jaehaerys was murdered?
With King Aegon.
And you were not
in the private quarters
where you might have
prevented the crime.
His Grace wished to entertain his companions
in the throne room.
But if you had thought
to go upstairs...
Where were you.
Lord Commander?
And why has Helaena the queen
been granted no sworn protector?
Surely once
she ascended. she...
Your brother is
a thief and a traitor
to the crown!
You well know
how it pains me.
How are we to know that
you do not secretly share
- his sentiments?
- I denounced him before the king.
We were one soul
in two bodies. yes.
If I'd shared his sentiments.
I would've fled with him.
First.
your brother betrays us.
And then
the young prince...
is murdered...
on your watch.
You are mad. Ser.
- Mad! You cannot think that I did this!
- What I think has no relevance!
You have brought disgrace
upon our ranks...
and now you must
restore it.
How am I to do that?
You will go
to Dragonstone
and strike down Rhaenyra
in her own halls.
The way she sought
to do with Aemond.
We will pay the princess back
in her own bloody coin.
- Alone?
- Does your courage fail you. Ser Arryk?
It's not a matter
of courage.
The castle is defended against all enemies.
now especially.
- How would I enter?
- Your twin serves there
at the pleasure
of the so-called queen.
They will mistake you for him
if you play the part.
We are sworn
to serve forthrightly.
not to traffic
in deception.
Put down
the pretender
and you will end a war
before it begins.
- If they see the two of us...
- You must not let that happen.
- You would send me to my death.
- Or to triumph.
And glory.
Now. will you go?
Or must I question
your loyalty to the king?
As you command...
my lord.
You missed supper.
I wasn't hungry.
I don't think
anyone was. really.
Too many
empty seats.
Do you know
where he went?
Harrenhal. I would think.
Sometimes I think
I hate him.
It's hard...
with fathers.
What do you remember
of my uncle?
He taught us to catch fish...
and sing
sailors' shanties.
He had a weakness
for cake.
And...
Ser Harwin Strong?
He was gentle.
and fierce.
They called him "Breakbones."
He loved us...
I think.
Of course. he did.
I miss Luke.
Daemon sent them
to kill me.
I was out.
You were with me.
In truth.
I am proud...
that he considers me
such a foe.
And that he seeks
to murder me in my bed.
He's afraid of me.
As well he should be.
The boy is grown
into a man.
Mm. No. Not here.
Hm.
I do regret that business
with Luke.
I lost my temper
that day.
I am sorry for it.
I am glad to hear it.
They used to tease me.
you know?
Because I was different.
I would remind you only that
when princes lose their temper.
it is often others
who suffer.
The smallfolk...
Like me.
How is she?
Much the same.
The markets have been running low
since the blockade.
Surely the city
cannot yet be short of food.
I think not.
but people are afraid.
Those with means are hoarding
everything they can.
I walked two hours today
to find a chicken for the pot
and paid three times
as much as I should have.
The selfishness
of people.
I cannot blame
anyone for doing
what I myself
would do if I could.
I don't think you'd
let children go hungry
while you filled
your own cellars.
Lucky we don't have
enough coin to find out.
The king has promised
us some relief.
Did he say when?
I'm afraid. Hugh.
I see all your
great adventures
have done nothing
for your looks.
Well met. brother.
after many months away.
I missed you.
Did you slay
many pirates?
Oh. more than you. to be sure.
Ha. a jest.
One you may regret
as you're supping alone tonight.
I regret it already.
I've broken my teeth
on hard tack. Addam.
Say you have a pot
of your goat stew simmering at home.
You're in luck.
In more ways than one.
I hear Lord Corlys himself commended you
for your service to him.
- He did.
- Will you sail with him
when his ship
has been repaired?
I am one of a dozen shipwrights
now called from Hull
to attend
with all speed to your fleet.
He made no offer.
And I would rather he didn't.
truth be told.
Do not be foolish. Alyn.
To serve with the Sea Snake
is to make your fortune.
Had I such a chance.
I would leap at it.
That's because you haven't seen
what I've seen.
There is a war
brewing. Addam.
- A real one.
- Another opportunity to distinguish yourself.
- Remind him of your worth.
- Oh. I need no favors.
But. brother.
he owes you. he owes us.
Does the stew have
carrots in it?
I mistrust this silence.
Daemon flies when we most need
his hand at the oar.
Devotion has never
sat well with him.
Where he goes.
he wishes to be his own master.
Well. he is
the king consort.
But he is not
the king.
Neither am I.
but I manage.
I too have felt
the crown pass over me.
It is a hard thing
to accept.
And now Viserys is dead
and all claims are in doubt.
You do not think...
Daemon will challenge her?
Not as such.
But neither can he allow
her to command him.
Pity.
I have. on occasion.
found that to be... quite enjoyable.
Let us take him
at his word.
If he can take Harrenhal.
all may well be forgiven.
In the meantime.
I am here.
And Meleys.
We will not let
the queen falter.
The lady Mysaria.
Your Grace.
You're aware of yesterday's events
in King's Landing?
I am.
Tell me what part you played
in their unfolding.
I had nothing
to do with it.
I know you are entwined
with the usurpers.
that you aided them
in denying me my birthright.
I took profits
from an inevitability.
I regret it now.
I'm sure you do.
Who are you?
A prisoner.
I gave Daemon two names.
That is the extent of it.
And I did not wish
to do that much.
He said it was
the price of my freedom.
Does he say otherwise?
He is gone.
For how long?
A week. or forever.
I do not know.
He does do that...
doesn't he?
You remember
me now.
He said he would
marry you.
- He said you carried his child.
- Not everyone found the jest funny.
And now it seems
he's done it again.
made a promise
and then slipped away.
You trade in the secrets
of the Red Keep.
Your web runs unseen
through King's Landing.
And now... when my enemy coils
himself to strike at me...
I can do nothing now
but ask you to honor
your husband's words.
It would not serve me
to set you free.
At best.
I lose an asset to my cause.
At worst.
you betray me in some foul way.
I have no interest
in betraying you. Your Grace.
So you say.
I was brought
to Westeros with nothing.
I toiled in service.
I stole.
I sold my own body
for coin or bread.
And I listened.
I collected confidences.
I made myself valuable to powerful men.
Bit by bit.
I earned my living.
A house.
a household. a home.
Then they set it
all aflame.
- Who did?
- The Hightowers. I can only assume.
The Hand... did not like it
when I showed my teeth.
But I thank him for it.
For too long. I made it
my aim to be of consequence.
But now. I see
that was the wish of a child.
Daemon.
Otto Hightower.
Makes no difference.
They will never
accept me.
I might as well
have remained a whore.
How did you get that scar?
Oh no.
My son.
- Who are they?
- Ratcatchers.
In the king's employ.
What'd they do?
What have you done?
The ratcatchers!
Oh... I had
them hanged.
The maggot who took
my son confessed to an accomplice.
He could not say
for certain which man it was. so...
- Idiot!
- Beware how you speak to your king. my lord.
The king is my grandson
and my grandson is a fool!
He's worse than a fool!
He's murdered innocent men!
- And one guilty one.
- And hanged them from the walls of the city for all to see!
Plot against the king.
and I will pay it back a hun...
They are fathers
and brothers and sons!
And their wives and children
gather now at our gates to weep
and curse your name!
With your
child's blood.
we bought
their approval.
With your
mother's tears.
we made a bitter sacrifice
against the deprivations
to come.
And you've thrown it away.
After all
I've done for you.
Thoughtless.
feckless...
self-indulgent.
At least I did something.
I have not answered
injury to the crown with. what?
Wailing and currying favor
with the fishwives?
I will not be thought weak.
Even now.
news of Rhaenyra's monstrous crime
spreads through the realm.
The great houses falter.
They cannot
but come to our side.
I wish to spill
blood. not ink!
We must act.
Ser Criston Cole
has acted.
And what... has
Ser Criston Cole done?
He has sent Ser Arryk
to slay Rhaenyra.
Alone?
He's pretending to be
his own twin. Brilliant.
Gods help us all.
It's time
the bitch queen paid a price.
And you acceded
to this. this prank
without consulting me
or the council?
Instead of judgment.
you display impetuousness.
and diminish us
in the eyes of our enemy!
Ill-considered. trifling!
Do you never think
of your father?
His...
forbearance. his...
judiciousness. his...
his... dignity.
Fuck dignity!
I want revenge.
My father is dead.
He is.
And we are
the poorer for it.
He was right about you.
He made me king.
Is that what you think?
Remove your badge. Ser Otto.
You were
my father's Hand.
Not mine.
Take it off.
You wouldn't dare.
I have dared...
and I find it
stimulating.
Insolent pup.
You think
yourself clever.
but without a strong
Hand at your side...
to guide?
Give it to Cole.
Your Grace?
In this hour.
you have proven yourself of more worth
than a hundred old men.
My new Hand
will be a steel fist.
You will regret this.
Give it to him.
You are dismissed.
I do not know if I trust you.
And I sense that
there is danger in you yet.
But I will keep
the word of my house
if you say that
it was given.
You may go.
Your Grace.
There's a Velaryon ship
in the harbor
bound for Myr
by way of Pentos.
I will see that you
are given passage.
I'm not so unworldly
as to let you fly free.
I am...
Thank you.
Ser Erryk. Mysaria
will be leaving us.
Let her collect
her things.
Then have someone
take her down
and secure her berth
on the "Corwyn."
Your Grace.
A moment.
Ser Erryk...
- I thought you were within.
- A sorry lack of vigilance.
The enemy is about.
good ser.
Please try and lay down.
Your Grace.
Thank you. Elinda.
Ser Erryk.
It's been
a strange day.
I'm restless.
I will stand this evening's duty.
You must sleep tonight.
Your Grace.
Let me ask the maester
for a draught.
Perhaps that
would be best.
Thank you. Elinda.
Ser Erryk?
Believe me...
I had no choice.
I don't understand.
Brother!
Do not do this.
I beg you.
You were the one
who betrayed us. Erryk.
Run. Elinda!
Run and find Ser Lorent!
- Your Grace!
- Ser Lorent!
With me. Your Grace!
Which?!
Which is Erryk?!
- We were born together.
- You parted us!
But I still
love you. brother.
Your Grace.
Erryk.
Forgive me.
No!
It is ignorance and vanity.
You know as well
as I do that Aegon must be kept in check.
As does Ser Criston.
The two of them together...
Ser Criston is
not temperate...
but his devotion
cannot be questioned.
- If it does come to war...
- He's ensured it.
He's young
and unschooled.
His faith is
in steel and bone.
He has not
the long view.
None of them do.
They wish now
not for the good of the realm.
but for the petty satisfaction
of vengeance.
Aegon is
still malleable.
It is the death of the child
that has unstrung him.
I can't stay here.
Exiled from the council.
Witness to
the blundering of our plans.
I'll return to Oldtown.
The Hightowers
still have strength.
and you have
a son there
who will take more
kindly to instruction.
Daeron may yet help us
in weeks to come.
Go rather
to Highgarden.
The Tyrells must
be taken in hand.
Their bannermen
are wavering.
While you're gone.
I'll speak sense to him.
His blood will cool.
In time.
you may yet return.
The young
are peacocks...
all shrieking
and feathers.
But we will yet prevail
and bring forth peace. I still believe it.
As long as you
and I hold fast.
I have sinned.
I do not wish
to hear of it.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm